<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Music on Daniel Parrish</title>
    <link>https://danielparrish.me/music/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Music on Daniel Parrish</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 16:45:58 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://danielparrish.me/music/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Fly (ft. AVANNA)</title>
      <link>https://danielparrish.me/music/fly/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Aug 2021 15:46:35 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://danielparrish.me/music/fly/</guid>
      <description>This is a song from the perspective of someone separated from their lover. Be it a short event or a more extended thing, it can be difficult to get through. I have a lot of respect for people in long-distance relationships. I don&amp;rsquo;t know if I would be able to do that.
&amp;ldquo;Fly&amp;rdquo; was originally written for Harvest Avanna, a VOCALOID community event celebrating Avanna, a native English-speaking voicebank.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trojan Horses (ft. Hatsune Miku)</title>
      <link>https://danielparrish.me/music/trojan-horses/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 11:25:18 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://danielparrish.me/music/trojan-horses/</guid>
      <description>A lot of my previous songs are happy and optimistic. That is partly as a reminder to me that things aren&amp;rsquo;t as bad as they seem. By contrast, &amp;ldquo;Trojan Horses&amp;rdquo; is a window into how mental illness can make you feel. Despite the tough subject matter, this song was fairly easy to write. I guess it&amp;rsquo;s easy to write about something that&amp;rsquo;s spent thousands of hours in your mind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sirius (ft. Kagamine Rin and Len)</title>
      <link>https://danielparrish.me/music/sirius/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2021 14:02:37 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://danielparrish.me/music/sirius/</guid>
      <description>It wouldn&amp;rsquo;t surprise me if one of the first thing most new vocalsynth producers do when they buy the Kagamines is to make some sort of duet. At least, that&amp;rsquo;s what I wanted to do. I always though the idea of 2 people, in different places, looking at the same thing in the sky was romantic. Couple that with the same 2 people trying to make sense of their feelings for each other, and you have &amp;ldquo;Sirius&amp;rdquo; in a nutshell.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maybe (ft. DAINA)</title>
      <link>https://danielparrish.me/music/maybe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Dec 2020 12:51:34 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://danielparrish.me/music/maybe/</guid>
      <description>I wrote the chorus for this song in late 2019 or early 2020. Initially, wasn&amp;rsquo;t sure how I wanted to handle the verses, so it sat unfinished for almost a year. The song was almost left unfinished, as I didn&amp;rsquo;t really like the lyrics a whole lot. However, I shared them online and got positive feedback, so I stuck with it and finished the song.
Going in, I didn&amp;rsquo;t have a plan for what &amp;ldquo;Maybe&amp;rdquo; would sound like.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Citrus Sunset (ft. Hatsune Miku)</title>
      <link>https://danielparrish.me/music/citrus-sunset/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2020 20:37:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://danielparrish.me/music/citrus-sunset/</guid>
      <description>This song was my entry in the MIKU EXPO 2020 Song Contest. Anybody could use Hatsune Miku&amp;rsquo;s voice in an original song and enter it in this contest. The winner would have Miku perform their song live during the MIKU EXPO 2020 concert. I actually used the free trial for this song, as I didn&amp;rsquo;t have the VOCALOID editor yet. While my song didn&amp;rsquo;t win, I still received a lot of kind words from people that liked it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smooth Romantic Way (ft. Eleanor Forte)</title>
      <link>https://danielparrish.me/music/smooth-romantic-way/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 15:11:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://danielparrish.me/music/smooth-romantic-way/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve always liked songs that tell a story. When I started writing &amp;ldquo;Smooth Romantic Way&amp;rdquo;, I wanted to tell the story of someone who wanted to confess their love to someone else, but things kept happening that prevented it. I think it turned out pretty funny.
This is the first song where I tried to use breath samples. Rather, I faked breath samples because the voice library for Eleanor Forte Lite doesn&amp;rsquo;t have any.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Red String of Fate (ft. Eleanor Forte)</title>
      <link>https://danielparrish.me/music/red-string-of-fate/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 11:12:38 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://danielparrish.me/music/red-string-of-fate/</guid>
      <description>The &amp;ldquo;red string of fate&amp;rdquo; is the idea that two people who are destined to be together are connected by a red string. It&amp;rsquo;s a popular idea often seen in Asian media, and being the anime fan that I am, I&amp;rsquo;ve run into it a few times. This song is about someone who has never found the person on the other end of their thread, but knows that one day they&amp;rsquo;ll meet them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Battle Cry (ft. Eleanor Forte)</title>
      <link>https://danielparrish.me/music/battle-cry/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 21:44:02 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://danielparrish.me/music/battle-cry/</guid>
      <description>This song means a little more to me than the others. I wrote it at a time where I was really struggling with some sin in my life. Eventually I reached a point where I was fed up. &amp;ldquo;Battle Cry&amp;rdquo; comes from my feelings as I cut ties with my old way of life and moved on to something better. I&amp;rsquo;m thankful to God for his mercy and grace, and I&amp;rsquo;m thankful to the other people in my life for their support.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Journey (ft. Eleanor Forte)</title>
      <link>https://danielparrish.me/music/the-journey/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 14:06:57 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://danielparrish.me/music/the-journey/</guid>
      <description>The latter half of 2019 into the first part of 2020 was a difficult time for me. I wrote &amp;ldquo;The Journey&amp;rdquo; as both a reminder to myself and a message to others that no matter what happens, everything is going to be fine. You may not know where you&amp;rsquo;re going, but as long as you&amp;rsquo;re moving, that&amp;rsquo;s progress. Keep going! And, don&amp;rsquo;t be afraid to get help. You&amp;rsquo;re worth helping.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pages (ft. Eleanor Forte)</title>
      <link>https://danielparrish.me/music/pages/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2020 09:31:06 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://danielparrish.me/music/pages/</guid>
      <description>This song is about a girl who has someone she likes, but is too shy to say anything to them. Instead of confessing her feelings, she writes them down in a notebook.
While &amp;ldquo;Soaring&amp;rdquo; was the first vocal synth song I released, &amp;ldquo;Pages&amp;rdquo; was actually written first. I sat on the lyrics for months, not really sure how I wanted it to sound. Eventually, I got tired of waiting and just dove in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Soaring (ft. Eleanor Forte)</title>
      <link>https://danielparrish.me/music/soaring/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2020 20:08:33 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://danielparrish.me/music/soaring/</guid>
      <description>I had the image in my head of someone daydreaming that they were flying with the one they have feelings for. They give them something to look forward to every day and lift them up when they&amp;rsquo;re feeling down.
This song is the result of a lot of &amp;ldquo;firsts&amp;rdquo; for me. It&amp;rsquo;s the first time working with vocal synthesis and the first time writing lyrics for anything. It&amp;rsquo;s far from the best song out there, but you gotta take that first step at some point.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blast Processed Otaku Tunes</title>
      <link>https://danielparrish.me/music/bpot/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2019 15:46:35 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://danielparrish.me/music/bpot/</guid>
      <description>deeepiii · Blast Processed Otaku TunesThis is a collection of 16-bit covers of songs featured in various Japanese anime. Each song (with one exception) was made entirely in Deflemask, a chiptune tracker that emulates old sound chips as closely as possible. In this case, those are the 2 sound chips found inside the Sega Genesis/Mega Drive. With the right tools, these songs could be played back on the original hardware.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blowin&#39; Off Dust</title>
      <link>https://danielparrish.me/music/blowin-off-dust/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2016 15:46:35 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://danielparrish.me/music/blowin-off-dust/</guid>
      <description>Back in 2016 my brother was running a tabletop RPG for some friends. Since they all lived in different places and couldn&amp;rsquo;t meet in-person, they used an online tabletop instead. At the time, that service had a built-in music player you could use to loop music. He made all the graphics himself in the style of an early 90s fantasy RPG, so I wrote some similarly-styled songs for him to use in-game.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
