<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>eleanor forte on Daniel Parrish</title>
    <link>https://danielparrish.me/tags/eleanor-forte/</link>
    <description>Recent content in eleanor forte on Daniel Parrish</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 15:11:03 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://danielparrish.me/tags/eleanor-forte/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Smooth Romantic Way (ft. Eleanor Forte)</title>
      <link>https://danielparrish.me/music/smooth-romantic-way/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 15:11:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://danielparrish.me/music/smooth-romantic-way/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve always liked songs that tell a story. When I started writing &amp;ldquo;Smooth Romantic Way&amp;rdquo;, I wanted to tell the story of someone who wanted to confess their love to someone else, but things kept happening that prevented it. I think it turned out pretty funny.
This is the first song where I tried to use breath samples. Rather, I faked breath samples because the voice library for Eleanor Forte Lite doesn&amp;rsquo;t have any.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Red String of Fate (ft. Eleanor Forte)</title>
      <link>https://danielparrish.me/music/red-string-of-fate/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 11:12:38 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://danielparrish.me/music/red-string-of-fate/</guid>
      <description>The &amp;ldquo;red string of fate&amp;rdquo; is the idea that two people who are destined to be together are connected by a red string. It&amp;rsquo;s a popular idea often seen in Asian media, and being the anime fan that I am, I&amp;rsquo;ve run into it a few times. This song is about someone who has never found the person on the other end of their thread, but knows that one day they&amp;rsquo;ll meet them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Battle Cry (ft. Eleanor Forte)</title>
      <link>https://danielparrish.me/music/battle-cry/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 21:44:02 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://danielparrish.me/music/battle-cry/</guid>
      <description>This song means a little more to me than the others. I wrote it at a time where I was really struggling with some sin in my life. Eventually I reached a point where I was fed up. &amp;ldquo;Battle Cry&amp;rdquo; comes from my feelings as I cut ties with my old way of life and moved on to something better. I&amp;rsquo;m thankful to God for his mercy and grace, and I&amp;rsquo;m thankful to the other people in my life for their support.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Journey (ft. Eleanor Forte)</title>
      <link>https://danielparrish.me/music/the-journey/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 14:06:57 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://danielparrish.me/music/the-journey/</guid>
      <description>The latter half of 2019 into the first part of 2020 was a difficult time for me. I wrote &amp;ldquo;The Journey&amp;rdquo; as both a reminder to myself and a message to others that no matter what happens, everything is going to be fine. You may not know where you&amp;rsquo;re going, but as long as you&amp;rsquo;re moving, that&amp;rsquo;s progress. Keep going! And, don&amp;rsquo;t be afraid to get help. You&amp;rsquo;re worth helping.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pages (ft. Eleanor Forte)</title>
      <link>https://danielparrish.me/music/pages/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2020 09:31:06 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://danielparrish.me/music/pages/</guid>
      <description>This song is about a girl who has someone she likes, but is too shy to say anything to them. Instead of confessing her feelings, she writes them down in a notebook.
While &amp;ldquo;Soaring&amp;rdquo; was the first vocal synth song I released, &amp;ldquo;Pages&amp;rdquo; was actually written first. I sat on the lyrics for months, not really sure how I wanted it to sound. Eventually, I got tired of waiting and just dove in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Soaring (ft. Eleanor Forte)</title>
      <link>https://danielparrish.me/music/soaring/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2020 20:08:33 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://danielparrish.me/music/soaring/</guid>
      <description>I had the image in my head of someone daydreaming that they were flying with the one they have feelings for. They give them something to look forward to every day and lift them up when they&amp;rsquo;re feeling down.
This song is the result of a lot of &amp;ldquo;firsts&amp;rdquo; for me. It&amp;rsquo;s the first time working with vocal synthesis and the first time writing lyrics for anything. It&amp;rsquo;s far from the best song out there, but you gotta take that first step at some point.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
